<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-GB"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-GB" /><updated>2019-06-16T08:21:15+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">TOTW</title><subtitle>Trees of the world, A site for learning about trees in different continents.</subtitle><author><name>DavidDarnes</name></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Trees of the World</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/general/2019/06/16/Welcome-to-Trees-of-the-World/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Trees of the World" /><published>2019-06-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/general/2019/06/16/Welcome-to-Trees-of-the-World</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/general/2019/06/16/Welcome-to-Trees-of-the-World/">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to TOTW. My goal for this blog is to research and discover trees from around the world. 
My goal is to release a series of blog posts weekly that will bring you BIG, small, interesting, or rare trees from around the world. 
I plan to provide you with a breif description of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Their location.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Their prefered habitat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An interesting fact about the tree and/or region.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The trees use, whether it be medicinal, construction, or some other resource.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join me on this adventure, and discover Trees of the world!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_Further Reading &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lists_of_trees&quot;&gt;Trees of Australia - Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>DavidDarnes</name></author><summary type="html">Welcome to TOTW. My goal for this blog is to research and discover trees from around the world. My goal is to release a series of blog posts weekly that will bring you BIG, small, interesting, or rare trees from around the world. I plan to provide you with a breif description of: Their location. Their prefered habitat. An interesting fact about the tree and/or region. The trees use, whether it be medicinal, construction, or some other resource. Join me on this adventure, and discover Trees of the world! _Further Reading Trees of Australia - Wikipedia</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/default-social-image.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A begginers WebDev experience</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/offtopic/2019/06/16/A-begginers-webdev-experience/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A begginers WebDev experience" /><published>2019-06-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/offtopic/2019/06/16/A-begginers--webdev-experience</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/offtopic/2019/06/16/A-begginers-webdev-experience/">&lt;p&gt;I know here at TOTW we are focused on learning and researching about trees from around the world but this all began as a hobby to learn the skills of web development. As that is the case, I’d like to share a little 
bit about how the website what built, it’s foundations and beginings. Origionally I was planing on building this website with a CSS framework, in particular &lt;a href=&quot;https://bulma.io/&quot;&gt;Bulma CSS&lt;/a&gt;. Using the Bulma framework, I was able to create very beautiful, repsonsive desktop and mobile compatible website. The learning curve was steep, as before this I had zero knowledge of HTML and CSS. As I have not&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>DavidDarnes</name></author><summary type="html">I know here at TOTW we are focused on learning and researching about trees from around the world but this all began as a hobby to learn the skills of web development. As that is the case, I’d like to share a little bit about how the website what built, it’s foundations and beginings. Origionally I was planing on building this website with a CSS framework, in particular Bulma CSS. Using the Bulma framework, I was able to create very beautiful, repsonsive desktop and mobile compatible website. The learning curve was steep, as before this I had zero knowledge of HTML and CSS. As I have not</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/default-social-image.png" /></entry></feed>